Guide to the Lee Family Papers, 1754-1836
Department of Special Collections
- ORIGINAL LETTERS AND DOCUMENTS
  - LEE, ELIZABETH AND N.V. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 6. 1793, Oct. 1.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Wm. [Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. sent clothing.
    - 7. [1794?], Mar. 23.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Wm. Lee. Courburg, Flander. A.L.S. Father's gout, Brother is appointed to the Government of Lord William in the Room of Gen. Murray.
    - 8. [1794], Aug. 1.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Capt. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. waiting to hear of Lee's promotion to Major, personal, Lady Harcourt, comments on unsuccessful campaign, death of cousin Mrs. Fiott.
    - 9. 1794, Sept. 18.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. congratulations on promotion, rumor B[arcré] guillotined, Lee's Senior officer wounded, Prince of Wale's intended marriage.
    - 10. 1794, Oct. 12.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Mrs. Harcourt's health, Lee's prospects for Lt. Col., Wm. has distinguished himself in his career.
    - 11. 1794, Nov. 12.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Father's gout, Lee still in command of Regiment, uncle Harcourt, Geo's house.
    - 12. 1794, Nov. 24.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. personal, no end of the success of the enemy, Miss Vernon is become Mrs. Vernon by being appointed Bedchamber Woman to our future Princess of Wales.
    - 13. 1794, Dec. 12.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Father, Mrs. Anson, we are all here very impatient for the meeting of Parliament which I suppose will determine the important business of either War or Peace, Uncle... has now the whole command of the British Forces, George's house.
    - 14. 1794,N.P. [E. Lee] to Capt. Lee c/o N. Collyer. London. forwarded upon the Continent cover.
    - 15. 1795, Apr. 13.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Cavalry does not return, [Harcourt] returning, difficulty in conveying letters, a scheme, Princess of Wales, Mrs. Harcourt to be present at Marriage ceremony.
    - 16. 1795, May 17.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Princess came over, Mrs. Stanhope.
    - 17. 1795, June 19.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. perhaps the poor Dauphins death may make a material difference, visitors.
    - 18. 1795, Aug. 21.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. at St. Leonards, good accounts of Lee from many including Lord Cathcart, an engagement, late disappointment (?), Harcourts, Mrs. Harcourt has not yet been at Nuneham, Lady Ford, George Anson must return to West Indies, Quiberon Bay, Amadie Harcourt, Mr. Fiott.
    - 19. 1795, Nov. 9.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Cavalry ordered home, Austrian victory attempt against King, Gen. to visit other brother and Lady Harcourt.
    - 20. 1795, Nov. 25.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Maj. Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. William to return, Aylesbury meeting, Lord Stanhope, Mr. Dudley, Lord Buckingham, Lord Grenville.
    - 21. 1797, Aug. 28.Nuneham. Elizabegh Lee to Wm. [Lee] N.P. A.L.S. visiting Lord and Lady Harcourt, other visits, asks Lee to call on his father, death of Lady Charles Fitzroy, Duke and Duchess of Harcourt, Princes and Victorino, Prince of [Westenburg?]
    - 22. 1797, Sept. 29.Hartwell. Elizabeth Lee to Lt. Col. Lee. Guildford. A.L.S. father cured mother of illness, eye operation, Queen, an unfortunate girl, rains.
    - 23. [1799?] Aug. 16.Nuneham. Elizabeth Lee to Wm. [Lee] N.P. A.L.S. Harcourts, health, late good Father, thanks for delivering plate, King and Queen.
    - 24. [1799, Aug.? - Sept.?]Nuneham. Elizabeth Lee to Sir Wm. Lee Bart. (IV) [Hartwell] A.L.S. health, taking plate to London, estate business.
    - 25. 1799, Sept. 6.Nuneham. Elizabeth Lee to Wm. [Lee] N.P. A.L.S. servants wages and other estate business re: giving her eldest brother a ring, Mr. Richards, thinning of the plantation.
    - 26. 1799, Sept. 27.N.P. [Elizabeth Lee] - Pin money account with numerous notes and memos: 1 s. Wm. Harcourt, Mar. 1, 1797,memo waiving claim for pin money.
    - 27. 1799, Dec. 13.St. Leonard's Hill. Elizabeth Lee to Wm. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. wants turkeys will pay for them.
    - 28. 1800, Jan. 3.[1799 on front] Queen St. Mayfair, London. Elizabeth Lee to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. wants feather bed etc. furniture, turkeys.
    - 29. [1800] Jan. 6.Queen St. [London] Elizabeth Lee to Wm. [Lee] N.P. A.L.S. her furniture and belongings from Hartwell, linen and sheets and other household items, dine with Stanhopes.
    - 30. 1800, Jan. 7.Queen St. [London] Elizabeth Lee. to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. sent linen, turkeys.
    - 31. 1800, Jan. 14.Queen St. [London] Elizabeth Lee to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. beds arrived.
    - 32. 1800,N.P. Elizabeth Lee to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. furniture.
    - 33. 1802, Jan.N.P. [Elizabeth Lee] A.N. on envelope.
    - 34. 1818, Mar. 11.Ilfracoombe. Nathaniel V. Lee to James Meek. London. A.L.S. financial, school committee, student who committed fraud.
  - LEE, GEORGE (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 1. 1778, July 2.Hartwell. George Lee to Master [Wm.] Lee. Harrow. A.L.S? health better, Fido caught two rabbits, Thame School.
    - 2. 1778, July 23.Hartwell. George Lee to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. broken fishing rod, storm, lightning.
    - 3. 1778, Oct. 8.Hartwell. George Lee to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. health, Uncle Harcourt has been married.
    - 4. 1778, Nov. 9.Hartwell. George Lee to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. storm.
    - 5. 1778, Nov. 19.Hartwell. George Lee to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. not going to school, dogs.
    - 6. 1779, Feb. 14.Hartwell. George Lee to [Wm.] Lee. Harrow. A.L.S. fishing rod, dogs, garden.
    - 7. 1780, Mar. 3.[London] George Lee to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. residents of Portland Place, Ashton Levey's museum.
    - 8. 1780, May 11.London. George Lee to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. King and Queen, christening of Lord _____?
    - 9. 1780, June 18.Hartwell. George Lee to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. mob about St. George's Fields, Portland Place strongly guarded.
    - 10. 1781, June 7.Portland Place [London] George Lee to [Wm.] Lee. Harrow. A.L.S. Mr. Bernard, dogs.
    - 11. [1783], Mar. 10.Hartwell. George Lee to Lt. Lee. King's Head Coventry. A.L.S. sending books etc, health.
    - 12. 1790, Jan. 30.Bristo St. George Lee to Cornet Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. Prickett, finances, bills at Oxford.
    - 13. 1790, Feb. 28. and Mar. 2.Bristo St. George Lee to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. business, Foxall, Smollett and Carmichael, Father has gotten one of George's bills.
    - 14. 1790, Aug. 15.Berwick. George Lee to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. delayed, journey, business.
    - 15. 1795, Jan. 6.Stone. George Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. re: medical vacancies, has gotten parsonage, needs money, marriage settlement.
    - 16. 1795, July 16.Stone. George Lee to Maj. Lee on foreign Service. A.L.S. finances, chance of peace.
    - 17. 1799, July 16.N.P. George Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. [London?] A.L.S. death of father - kidney trouble.
    - 18. 1802, Sept. 24.Sir George Lee - Trust - D.S. account of advances from Elizabeth to trustees s. Wm. Harcourt, S. Bernard and George Lee.
    - 19. N.D., July 14.Bristo St. George Lee to Cornet Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. election for Dumfrieshire Miller for Duke of Queensberry vs. James Johnstone, Burgh election results.
    - 20. [1790?] July 24.Bristo St. George Lee to Cornet Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. unable to get into Holyrood House for the election of the Scotish Peers, no word of Dumfrieshire election, financial business.
    - 21. N.D.N.P. George Lee to Lt. Lee. Blackheath. A.L.S. business at hospital, Review.
    - 22. N.D., Jan. 11.New [Hummarms?] George Lee to Lt. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. business.
    - 23. N.D. June 14.Hartwell. George Lee to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. business, William apparently headed overseas.
    - 24. [1794], Apr. 2[7]Hartwell. George Lee to Capt. Lee. London. A.L.S. William on Continent, Dr. Moore - an extraction East of Temple Bar, George's house being built, news of victory near Landr_____?
    - 25. [1794], Sept. 21.Hartwell. George Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. congratulations on promotion, business work on house, to be in vicarage in six weeks, (William on Continent).
    - 26. N.D.Hartwell. George Lee to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. Carlo.
    - 27. [1799], July 6.N.P. George Lee to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. father's disorder - will probably die in a few hours, note added later confirms death.
    - 28. N.D.N.P. George Lee to Master Lee. Harrow. A.L.S. health, Lord Chesterfield borrowed books, dogs.
    - 29. N.D., June 9.Hartwell. George Lee to Wm. Lee. St. Hohns College, Cambridge. A.L.S. cheese, shirt, health.
    - 30. N.D.N.P. George Lee to Wm. Lee N.P. A.L.S.
    - 31. N.D.N.P. George Lee to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. things sent gone astray, Parker's son, finances, Wm. going to Canterbury, charger lost lameness Lilly had two white puppies.
    - 32. N.D.N.P. George Lee to Wm. Lee N.P. A.L.S. sending things, racing.
    - 33. N.D., May 16.N.P. George Lee to Capt. Lee. Ostend. A.L.S. business.
    - 34. N.D. Mar. 23.Hartwell. [George Lee] to [Wm. Lee] N.P. A.L. frag. puppy, medicine, letter about France seen by Father, a scheme, to visit the Bishop has determined to be cropt (enter church).
  - LEE, WILLIAM III 1762 - 1785 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 1. 1762, Dec. 9.David Street. W. Lee to [R. Antonie] Colworth. A.L.S. re: Sheriff elections.
    - 2. 1762, Dec. 22.David Street. W. Lee to Rd. Antonie. Colworth. A.L.S. sends information very little danger of your being Sheriff, Duke of Bedford.
    - 3. 1768, Sept.?.High Donn. [W.] Lee to Mr. Anthony. Colworth. A.L. accepts invitation.
    - 4. [1771?] Apr. 13.Hartwell. W. Lee to [Wm. Lee Antonie] A.L.S. Wm. Lee Antonie to visit, re: travelling, advice.
    - 5. 1776, July 21.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. [Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. health, school, puppies.
    - 6. 1776, Nov. 29.Hartwell. W. Lee. to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. health, frost, puppy, clothing.
    - 7. 1777, July 20.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. [Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. determined not to leave you at Harrow after your Breaking up, Lords and Ladys Harcourt and Nuneham invited William and George to Nuneham, father going to Ld. Vernon's in Derbyshire.
    - 8. 1778, June 23.Hartwell. W. Lee to William [Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. repairing house, George now well, school, Bishop of Lincoln.
    - 9. 1778, July 12.Hartwell. W. Lee to William [Lee] N.P. A.L.S. George, Jack, expect Col. Harcourt, advice.
    - 10. 1778, Aug. 6.Lee Estate - document. re: inheritance of Wm. Lee III, will?
    - 11. 1778, Dec. 6.Hartwell. W. Lee to William Lee. N.P. A.L.S.
    - 12. [1779 or 81]N.P. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Easton, Stamford. A.L.S. Antonie's sisters, library, avoid Novels, new Administration.
    - 13. 1779, Aug. 15.N.P. W. Lee to Thomas Bernard. N.P. A.L.S. re: a power of attorney, whist.
    - 14. 1779, Dec. 19.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Easton, Stamford. A.L.S. Mr. Skinner, Lees cousins of Antonie, advice and correction rent of Colworth.
    - 15. 1781, Apr. 12.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Easton, Stamford. A.L.S. compliments. Antonie's last tour.
    - 16. 1781, Oct. 18.Nuneham. W. Lee to Wm. Lee. St. John's College, Cambridge. A.L.S. Cambridge apartment, plantations.
    - 17. 1781, Nov. 4.Hartwell. W. Lee to [Wm. Lee] [Cambridge] A.L.S. Cambridge, advice, Mr. Skinner, guard against contagion of Example, making friends.
    - 18. 1781, Nov. 12.Hartwell. W. Lee to [? Wm. Lee] [Cambridge] A.L.S. frag. advice re: finances.
    - 19. 1781, Dec. 25.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee. Cambridge. A.L.S. frag. reprimand for remaining at Cambridge against father's wishes.
    - 20. 1782, May 27.London. W. Lee to William [Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. wages, son to attend chapel, spend part of vacation in study, a horse, Sir John Griffin, Mr. Pearce, Admiral Rodney's success and Hoods, violent cold - widespread.
    - 21. 1782, Oct. 6.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. advice, Mrs. Lee.
    - 22. 1783, Feb. 1.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. Antonie's involvement in politics.
    - 23. 1783, Apr. 24.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. A.L.S. re: traveling plans, include Scotland and Ireland.
    - 24. 1783, July 20.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Easton. A.L.S. advice.
    - 25. 1783, Aug. 3.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. at Mr. Skinners. A.L.S. plan of education, authors, Moliere, Handel, criticism, cows.
    - 26. 1783, Oct. 19.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Jesus College, Cambridge. A.L.S. university, Mr. Skinner, allowance.
    - 27. 1783, Nov. 11.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. allowance, advice.
    - 28. 1783, Nov. 30.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. cash, vacation, Mr. Skinner.
    - 29. 1783, Dec. 11.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. education, advice, learning French.
    - 30. 1783, Dec. 28.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. advice.
    - 31. 1784, Feb. 17.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. [Cambridge] A.L.S. advice, law lectures, accounts.
    - 32. 1784, Mar. 28.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S.
    - 33. 1784, Apr. 29.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. an escape, elections, county battle?
    - 34. 1784, June [16]Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. Mr. Delon, excursion plans.
    - 35. 1784, June 22.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. trip plans, advice.
    - 36. 1784, July 18.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. a marriage proposal to Wm. Lee Antonie's sister, asks Antonie's opinion of the man.
    - 37. 1784, Sept. 6.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. recommendations from Duke of Portland.
    - 38. 1784, Sept. 7.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. Mr. Powys.
    - 39. 1784, Sept. 28.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. reprimand.
    - 40. 1784, Dec. 30.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Cambridge. A.L.S. plans for future, advice.
    - 41. 1785, Jan. 4.N.P. W. Lee to [Elizabeth Lee] N.P. A.L.S. affectionate, instructions in case of death.
    - 42. 1792, July 12.W. Lee. Document. copy of will made by Wm. Lee(son) and George Lee and signed by them, enclosed with #41, with additions Dec. 29, 1798, June 26, 1799.
    - 43. 1792, July 13.N.P. W. Lee. Document. copy of a memo made and signed by Wm. Lee (son) and George Lee, enclosed with #41, clarification of will.
    - 44. 1785, Jan. 6.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie, London. A.L.S. reprimand, palns, presentation at Court.
    - 45. 1785, Feb. 17.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. trip, good wishes.
    - 46. 1785, July 13.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. [Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. small pox at Harrow.
  - LEE, WILLIAM (III) 1786 - 1798 and N.D. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - 1. 1786, Mar. 24.N.P. [Wm. Lee III] Doc. frag. re: Lee-Antonie estate, guardianship of Wm. Lee Antonie etc, opinions, s. J.P. and Samuel Phipps.
    - 2. 1786, May 28.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. dangers, estate business.
    - 3. 1786, June 1.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. estate, [end of guardianship], some better scheme of settlement for the young Ladies.
    - 4. 1786, Aug. 2.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Margate, A.L.S. personal.
    - 5. 1786, Aug. 27.Hartwell. W. Lee Antonie. Isle of Thanet. A.L.S. book of maps, business.
    - 6. 1786, Sept. 21.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. my son is going to spend the Winter at Strasbourg for military education, asks Mr. Delon to accompany him.
    - 7. 1786, Sept. 24.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. re: son's trip.
    - 8. 1786, Oct. 1.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. re: Miss Sophia.
    - 9a. 1786, Dec. 19.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. business.
    - 9b. [1786?].[Hartwell]. [W. Lee] to Wm. [Lee]. [Strasbourg] A.L. Mr. Delon et al, Strasbourg argument, maxims, advice, education.
    - 10. 1787, Jan. 6.Hartwell. W. Lee to John Fiott. London. A.L.S. Lee Antonie's friends, business.
    - 11. 1789, May 8.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee. [London?]. A.L.S. worry.
    - 12. 1789, June 7.N.P. W. Lee to Wm. Lee c/o General Harcourt. London. A.L.S. pride in son, gout.
    - 13. 1789, June 12.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee. London. A.L.S. health, Lady Vernon, colt, King.
    - 14. 1789, Aug. 5.N.P. W. Lee to Cornet Lee. Lewes. A.L.S. recovery, garden room finished, comments on France and revolution.
    - 15. [1789, prior to Oct.?]N.P. W. Lee to [Wm. Lee Antonie] N.P. A.L.S. book of maps.
    - 16. 1789, Oct. 22.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. book of maps, family and sisters, advice, neglect caused by a woman, closer confinement than even the moaarch of the French.
    - 17. 17[90], Apr. 30.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. [Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. accounts with Mr. Ryder, etc., borrowing from son, purchasing land.
    - 18. 1790, June 2.Hartwell. W. Lee to Cornet Lee. Tunbridge. A.L.S. Irish snuff, William to visit for a month.
    - 19. 1790, Sept. 17.Hartwell. W. Lee to Cornet Lee. Maidstone. A.L.S. Anson, Harcourts.
    - 20. 1792, July 12.[W. Lee]. A.D. list of debts exclusive of mortgages with notes.
    - 21. 1793, Mar. 27.Hartwell. W. Lee to Lt. Lee. London. A.L.S. Wm. ordered overseas.
    - 22. 1794, June 8.Hartwell. W. Lee to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. negotiation for majority.
    - 23. 1794, June 30.Hartwell. W. Lee to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. accounts, death of Mrs. Fiott.
    - 24. 1794, July 15.Hartwell. W. Lee to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. no talk of peace, Parliament, Mrs. Fiott's death, storm.
    - 25. 1794, July 27.Hartwell. W. Lee to Capt. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. waiting to hear of promotion, William commanding Regiment.
    - 26. 1794, Aug. 27.Hartwell. W. Lee to Capt. Lee.N.P. A.L.S. still looking for promotion, downfall of Robspiere [sic], London riots, Prince Coburg's victory.
    - 27. 1794, Sept. 12.[Hartwell]. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. congratulations on promotion, cmd. of Regiment, Prince of Wale's marriage with Princess of Brunswick and A.N.S. by E. Lee.
    - 28. 1794, Oct. 30.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. with Duke of York's Army. A.L.S. promotion of St. Leger, Gen. Cailla[es?], the good and proper effect of civilized War, vicarage at Stone nearly ready.
    - 29. 1794, Nov. 20.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. gout - cannot walk or stand, George gone to Oxford.
    - 30. 1794, Dec. 6.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. vicarage, Ansons.
    - 31. 1795, Jan. 4.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee N.P. A.L.S. severe weather, health, sad state of the world - happier far, perhaps it may be for those going out of the world than those coming into it, defection of the Dutch, George at vicarage.
    - 32. 1794, Jan. 4.[Hartwell]. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Squire Thompson a soldier at Bombay under Cornwallis.
    - 33. 1795, Jan. 21.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. William not immediately concerned in the late fierce Engagements.
    - 34. 1795, Mar. 7.[Hartwell]. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. retreat, difficult communication, Lord and Lady Harcourt, the struggle, Anson arrived from Jamaica.
    - 35. 1795, Apr. 7.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Harcourts return to England, Lt. Col. Affleck appointed in room of Sir Robert Laurey [sic], owes money to son.
    - 36. 1795, May 22.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. Germany. A.L.S. promotions, will talk to Harcourt.
    - 37. 1795, July 10.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. William passed over for Lt. Col. - unavoidable by Harcourt, leave of absence not practical, all parties will be starved into peace, cold weather, exertions in relief of the poor, victories of Lord Bridport and fleet and Cornwallis.
    - 38. 1795, Aug. 12.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. question of peace, Lady Ford, Ld. Cathcart's favorable comment on William at inundation.
    - 39. 1795, Oct. [20].Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. Germany. A.L.S. asks word of another soldier, son of Betty.
    - 40. 1795, Oct. 25.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. agriculture, harvest, and prices, Levant Fleet disaster, rumors of a pacifist tendency.
    - 41. 1795, Nov. 15.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. success of General [Clerfaye] and [Wurmser], attempt on King's life.
    - 42. 1796, Mar. 29.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. William's location, Gen. Gwynn, personal business.
    - 43. 1796, Apr. 12.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S.
    - 44. 1796, May 29.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. must discuss business.
    - 45. 1796, June 9.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. London. A.L.S. inoculating in Aylesbury.
    - 46. 1796, Aug. 22.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. personal.
    - 47. 1796, Oct. 10.Hartwell. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. Henley. A.L.S. William should be freer in his letters home, too suspicious.
    - 48. 1796, Dec. 21Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Bedford. A.L.S. advice re: Trust Fund, stocks, Estate, in Norfolk, Edgeware Estate.
    - 49. 1796, Dec. 4.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Bedford. A.L.S. business and financial advice, Fiott and [de] Gruchy.
    - 50. 1796, Dec. 14.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. N.P. A.L.S. re: [Norfolk Estate].
    - 51. 1797, Feb. 15.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. Fiott's affairs.
    - 52. 1797, Apr. 7.[Hartwell]. W. Lee to Maj. Lee. Beaconsfield. A.L.S. will keep secret.
    - 53. 1797, Apr. 11.[Hartwell]. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. sales at Totteridge, Trust Fund.
    - 54. 1797, Apr. 30.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Bedford. A.L.S. business.
    - 55. 1798, Feb. 3.Hartwell. W. Lee to Wm. [Lee]. N.P. A.L.S. coachman/butcher, places for tenants, etc.
    - 56. 1798, Aug. 17.Hartwell. W. Lee to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor Castle. A.L.S. Duke of Portland's ball, personal.
    - 57. 1798, Sept. 18.[Hartwell]. W. Lee to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. sick animal.
    - 58. N.D.N.P. Wm. Lee [III?] to Thomas Bernard. N.P. A.L. legal business.
    - 59. N.D.N.P. W. Lee to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. colt and filley, Aylesbury election - Col. Lake and Scrope Bernard, Lee Antonie for Marlow, local politics.
    - 60. N.D., Sept. 8.N.P. W. Lee to William Lee. N.P. A.L.S. sick horse, William to come home via Cambridge, Sir John Griffin, trouble, William's first tour.
    - 61. N.D.N.P. [W. Lee?] to [Wm. Lee?]. [Harrow?]. A.L. frag. medicine and instructions.
    - 62. N.D., May3.N.P. W. Lee to William [Lee]. N.P. A.N.S. sends packet.
    - 63. N.D., May 22.N.P. W. Lee to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. wishes William and George a good journey.
    - 64. N.D.,N.P. Lee to Wm. Lee. [Harrow]. A.L.S. to come home.
    - 65. N.D.N.P. W. Lee to Wm. [Lee]. [Harrow]. A.L.S. George's illness, 4th form, death of Lady Bernard.
    - 66. N.D.N.P. W. Lee to Wm. [Lee]. N.P. Wm. and George returned to school, strawberries.
  - LEE, WILLIAM (IV) 1780 - 1796 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - 1. 1780, Sept. 7.Harrow. W. Lee (IV) to [W. L. III]. N.P. A.L.S. journey to Harrow, election.
    - 2. 1781, Sept. 6.[Rundle?]. W. Lee to [W.L. III]. N.P. A.L.S. journey, horse in pain.
    - 3. 1781, Oct. 15.Cambridge. William Lee to [W.L. III]. N.P. A.L.S. tutor, chambers, should treat in the publick hall.
    - 4A. 1786, Jan. 18.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. concern difficulty with liquidation of mortgage.
    - 4B. 1786, Aug. 3.Hartwell. William Lee to Mr. Hodgekinson. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) financial arrangements.
    - 5A. 1786, June 8.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to Wm Lee Antonie London re: return of Mr. [Fiott?].
    - 5B. 1786, Aug. 13.Hartwell. William Lee to Thomas Ryder. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) financial business.
    - 6. 1787, May 10.Strasbourg. Wm. Lee to Munro. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) re: leave of absence.
    - 7. 1788, Oct. 10.Vienna. Wm. Lee to Vassar. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) finances, friendship, plea for help.